module.exports = [
  {
    question: 'Who was Fiorello La Guardia?', 
    a: 'A NYC mayor',
    b: 'A Famous Pilot',
    c: 'A Famous Author',
    d: 'An Attorney General',
    answer: 'a'
  },
  {
    question: 'Who wrote the 1965 song "Ticket to Ride"?', 
    a: 'The Beatles',
    b: 'ABBA',
    c: 'The Beach Boys',
    d: 'Black Sabbath',
    answer: 'a'
  },
  {
    question: 'What is a diverse underwater ecosystem held together by calcium carbonate?', 
    a: 'Algal Bloom',
    b: 'Coral Reef',
    c: 'Aquaculture',
    d: 'Benthic Zone',
    answer: 'b'
  },
  {
    question: 'Who was Nicole Kidman\'s first husband?', 
    a: 'Keith Urban',
    b: 'Billy Bob Thornton',
    c: 'Brad Pitt',
    d: 'Tom Cruise',
    answer: 'd'
  },
  {
    question: 'According to Dante, how many circles of Hell are there?', 
    a: 'Six',
    b: 'Nine',
    c: 'Seven',
    d: 'Ten',
    answer: 'b'
  },
  {
    question: 'Who voiced Mr. Potato Head in the Toy Story movies?', 
    a: 'Tom Hanks',
    b: 'Hank Azaria',
    c: 'Andy Rooney',
    d: 'Don Rickles',
    answer: 'd'
  },
  {
    question: 'Which battery company first featured a pink rabbit as their mascot?', 
    a: 'Duracell',
    b: 'Panasonic',
    c: 'Rayovac',
    d: 'Energizer',
    answer: 'a'
  },
  {
    question: 'Plastics are also known as _____', 
    a: 'Saccharides',
    b: 'Polymers',
    c: 'Alkaloids',
    d: 'Isomers',
    answer: 'b'
  },
  {
    question: 'Which of the following is NOT a variety of apples?', 
    a: 'Fiji',
    b: 'Gala',
    c: 'McIntosh',
    d: 'Braeburn',
    answer: 'a'
  },
  {
    question: 'Fred Astaire and Gene Kelly were best known for what?', 
    a: 'Psychology',
    b: 'Astronomy',
    c: 'Dancing',
    d: 'Cooking',
    answer: 'c'
  },
];